http://www.utahhumane.org/privacy-policy

Skip to main content
Privacy Policy
You are hereHome
Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, the Humane Society of Utah (HSU) has developed this Privacy Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate, disclose and make use of your personal information. We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with this policy in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained. If you would like to stop receiving any method of communication by mail, phone or email, please contact Kayla Smith, Associate Director of Development, at kayla@utahhumane.org or 801-506-2414.
We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.
We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.
We will NEVER share personal information with a third-party.
Before or at the time of collecting personal information when making a donation, attending an event, or utilizing our adoption and clinic services, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected. Personal information collected includes, full name, mailing address, phone number and email address.
We will collect and use personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified, and we will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.
We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.
